Kaufman, Jacob J. Papers 6190
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jacob J. Kaufman Papers
1949-1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kaufman, Jacob J.
6190
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Papers.
8398280
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 20, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 24, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Kaufman, Jacob Joseph
8398280
- Publications on Education, Employment, and General Labor Issues. (Box 1)
  - Academic Tenure (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Academic Tenure, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Language: English.
  - The Application of Cost-Effectiveness Techniques to Adult Basic Education in Correctional Institutions, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: The Application of Cost-Effectiveness Techniques to Adult Basic Education in Correctional Institutions, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman; Kenneth H. Neagle
      Notes: Paper presented at Adult Basic Education in Correctional Institutions conference, October 8-9, 1969.
      Format: Publication
  - Better Options, Better Lives, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Better Options, Better Lives, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Author: Advisor Council on Education
      Notes: Summary Report on the Needed Reform in Occupational Education in Massachusetts.
    - Item 2: Better Options, Better Lives, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: Summary Report on the Needed Reform in Occupational Education in Massachusetts. Copy 2.
  - Cost-Effectiveness Analysis as a Method for the Evaluation of Vocational and Technical Education, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Cost-Effectiveness Analysis as a Method for the Evaluation of Vocational and Technical Education, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman
      Notes: Paper presented at American Vocational Association annual meeting, October 8, 1968.
    - Item 2: Cost-Effectiveness Analysis as a Method for the Evaluation of Vocational and Technical Education, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: Paper presented at American Vocational Association annual meeting, October 8, 1968. Copy 2.
    - Item 3: Cost-Effectiveness Analysis as a Method for the Evaluation of Vocational and Technical Education, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: Published in Journal of Industrial Teacher Education v.6:no.3 (1969:Spring)
    - Item 4: Cost-Effectiveness Analysis as a Method for the Evaluation of Vocational and Technical Education, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: Published in Journal of Industrial Teacher Education v.6:no.3 (1969:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Cost-Effectiveness of Vocational Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Cost-Effectiveness of Vocational Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Critical Issues in Vocational and Technical Education, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Critical Issues in Vocational and Technical Education, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Notes: Paper presented at the Teacher Education Institute, Agricultural and Technical College, July 24, 1967.
  - Developing Programs and Training Teachers for the Disadvantages, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Developing Programs and Training Teachers for the Disadvantages, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Notes: Published in Pennsylvania School Journal v.117:no.7 (1969:Mar.)
  - An Economist Looks at Hight Education, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: An Economist Looks at Hight Education, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Notes: Paper presented at The President's Seminar on " The Economics of Higher Education with Special Reference to the Junior College" June 22, 1967.
    - Item 2: An Economist Looks at Hight Education, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Notes: Paper presented at The President's Seminar on " The Economics of Higher Education with Special Reference to the Junior College" June 22, 1967. Copy 2
  - The Economy and the College Graduate, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: The Economy and the College Graduate, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: Paper presented at the annual meeting of the Eastern College Personnel Officers, October 6, 1971.
  - Education Reform for the 1970's, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Education Reform for the 1970's, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Effect of Collective Bargaining on the Issue of "Excellence or Equality" in Higher Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: The Effect of Collective Bargaining on the Issue of "Excellence or Equality" in Higher Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman; Patricia Flannery
      Notes: Paper contributed to the working party on Roles and Functions and the Organization of the University at the 3rd International Conference on Higher Education at the University of Lancaster, England, September 1-5, 1975.
    - Item 2: The Effect of Collective Bargaining on the Issue of "Excellence or Equality" in Higher Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Notes: Paper contributed to the working party on Roles and Functions and the Organization of the University at the 3rd International Conference on Higher Education at the University of Lancaster, England, September 1-5, 1975. Copy 2.
  - Girls and Vocational Education, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Girls and Vocational Education, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Notes: Published in Women's Education, v.5:no.4 (1966:Dec.)
  - The High School Diploma: Credential for Employment?, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: The High School Diploma: Credential for Employment?, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman; Morgan V. Lewis
      Notes: June 1972.
  - Human Resource Development and Vocational Education, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Human Resource Development and Vocational Education, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Notes: May 1975.
    - Item 2: Human Resource Development and Vocational Education, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Notes: May 1975. Copy 2.
  - Internal Barriers to the Implementation of a PPB System in a University, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Internal Barriers to the Implementation of a PPB System in a University, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Notes: Paper presented at a Conference on Decision-Making in Higher Education, August 21, 1969.
  - Investment in Vocational Educaton, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Investment in Vocational Educaton, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Notes: Paper presented at a Conference on New Labor Market Entrants: Problems and Policies, March 19-20, 1970, Indiana University
    - Item 2: Investment in Vocational Educaton, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Notes: Paper presented at a Conference on New Labor Market Entrants: Problems and Policies, March 19-20, 1970, Indiana University. Copy 2.
  - Is U.S. Vocational Education Measuring Up To the Need?, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Is U.S. Vocational Education Measuring Up To the Need?, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman; Carl J. Schaefer
      Notes: Published in School Shop, v. 27:no.1 (1967:Sep.)
  - Job Placement and Employment Experience of High School Graduates, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Job Placement and Employment Experience of High School Graduates, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Notes: A preliminary report presented at a Conference on Research in Vocational and Technical Education, June 10-11, 1966.
  - Making the Right to Read a Reality, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Making the Right to Read a Reality, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Item 2: Making the Right to Read a Reality, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Notes: Copy 2.
  - Manpower Information for Occupational Education Planning, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Manpower Information for Occupational Education Planning, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Notes: Paper presented at the Researchers' Conference in Vocational-Technical Education, October 29, 1971.
  - The Massachusetts Information System for Occupational Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: The Massachusetts Information System for Occupational Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Obstacles to Change: Some Relevant Comments Based on Research on the "Disadvantaged", 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Obstacles to Change: Some Relevant Comments Based on Research on the "Disadvantaged", 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
      Notes: Paper presented at a Conference on Rehabilitation, Sheltered Workshops and the Disadvantaged, February 16-18, 1970.
  - Occupational Training, Changing Life-Styles, Job Satisfaction, and Worker Productivitiy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Occupational Training, Changing Life-Styles, Job Satisfaction, and Worker Productivitiy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Occupational Training Needs for Youth, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Occupational Training Needs for Youth, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Notes: Published in Journal of Human Resources, Supplement, 1968.
    - Item 2: Occupational Training Needs for Youth, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Notes: Published in Journal of Human Resources, Supplement, 1968. Copy 2.
  - Outside Prison Walls: Ex-Offenders in Transition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Outside Prison Walls: Ex-Offenders in Transition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Potential of Vocational Education, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: The Potential of Vocational Education, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
      Notes: Reprinted from The Bulletin of the National Association of Secondary School Principals, v.53:no.334 (1969:Feb.).
    - Item 2: The Potential of Vocational Education, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
      Notes: Reprinted from The Bulletin of the National Association of Secondary School Principals, v.53:no.334 (1969:Feb.). Copy 2.
    - Item 3: The Potential of Vocational Education, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
      Notes: Reprinted from The Bulletin of the National Association of Secondary School Principals, v.53:no.334 (1969:Feb.). Copy 3.
  - Research in Vocational-Technical Education: Economic Implications, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Research in Vocational-Technical Education: Economic Implications, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Notes: Paper presented at the New Jersey Researchers' Conference on Vocational Education, October 29, 1971.
  - The Role of Cost-Benefit Analysis in the Evaluation of Vocational and Technical Education, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: The Role of Cost-Benefit Analysis in the Evaluation of Vocational and Technical Education, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
      Notes: Paper presented at American Vocational Association annual meeting, December 5, 1967.
    - Item 2: The Role of Cost-Benefit Analysis in the Evaluation of Vocational and Technical Education, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
      Notes: Paper presented at American Vocational Association annual meeting, December 5, 1967. Copy 2.
  - The Role of Economics in the Training of Leaders in the Field of Vocational and Technical Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: The Role of Economics in the Training of Leaders in the Field of Vocational and Technical Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - The Role of the Secondary Schools in the Preparation of Youth for Work, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: The Role of the Secondary Schools in the Preparation of Youth for Work, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
      Notes: Paper presented at American Vocational Association annual meeting, December 8, 1966.
  - The School Environment and Programs for Dropouts: Summary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: The School Environment and Programs for Dropouts: Summary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman; Morgan V. Lewis; David C. Gumpper
  - Sex Discrimination and Sex Stereotyping in Vocational Education, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: Sex Discrimination and Sex Stereotyping in Vocational Education, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
      Notes: Prepared statement by Jacob J. Kaufman, April 21, 1975
  - Statement Before the General Subcommittee on Education, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: Statement Before the General Subcommittee on Education, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
      Notes: Prepared statement by Jacob J. Kaufman, February 1, 1968.
  - Teacher Attitudes and School Dropouts, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: Teacher Attitudes and School Dropouts, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
      Notes: Paper presented at American Vocational Association annual meeting, December 7, 1966.
  - The Use of Paperbacks in the Introductory Course in Economics, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: The Use of Paperbacks in the Introductory Course in Economics, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - The Bituminous Coal Industry: A Manpower Forecast, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: The Bituminous Coal Industry: A Manpower Forecast, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
      Notes: Paper presented at the 1977 Mining Convention, September 13, 1977.
  - Changing Workforce Requirements in West Virginia, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: Changing Workforce Requirements in West Virginia, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - The Closing of the Ford Motor Company Plant in Mahwah, NJ, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: The Closing of the Ford Motor Company Plant in Mahwah, NJ, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
      Author: Stephen Levine; Alice Beamsderfer; Jacob J. Kaufman
      Notes: January 1983.
    - Item 2: The Closing of the Ford Motor Company Plant in Mahwah, NJ, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
      Notes: January 1983. Copy 2.
    - Item 3: The Closing of the Ford Motor Company Plant in Mahwah, NJ, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
      Notes: January 1983. Copy 3.
  - Chronic Unemployment in Pennsylvania, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: Chronic Unemployment in Pennsylvania, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
      Notes: Published in The Pennsylvania State University Bulletin, v.53:no.17 (1959:Oct.)
  - Discussion on the Elimination of Poverty, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: Discussion on the Elimination of Poverty, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Notes: Reprinted from the 1966 Social Statistics Section Proceedings of the American Statistical Society
  - Discussion on Unemployment Reduction, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: Discussion on Unemployment Reduction, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
      Notes: Published in American Economic Review, v.50:no.2 (1960:May)
  - Displacement of Workforce and Collective Bargaining: Myths and Realities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: Displacement of Workforce and Collective Bargaining: Myths and Realities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
      Notes: Paper for a Ford Foundation Faculty Research Fellowship in 1962-1963
  - The Effect of Prison Environment on the Establishment of Grievance Procedures for Inmates, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: The Effect of Prison Environment on the Establishment of Grievance Procedures for Inmates, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
      Notes: Paper presented before the American Society of Criminology, November 2, 1974.
  - An Evaluation of the Ex-Offenders Program of the East Harlem Community Corporation, 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: An Evaluation of the Ex-Offenders Program of the East Harlem Community Corporation, 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
      Author: Monte Rivera; James Jennings; Alice Beamsderfer; Jacob J. Kaufman
      Notes: May 1978.
  - A Framework for Change, 1980; Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Item 1: A Framework for Change, 1980; Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
      Author: Joel Gershenfeld; Len Mayer
  - Improving Federal Evaluation Planning, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Item 1: Improving Federal Evaluation Planning, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
      Author: Garth Buchanan; Pamela Horst; Johnn Scanlon
      Notes: Reprinted from Evaluation, v.1:no.2 (1973)
    - Item 2: Improving Federal Evaluation Planning, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
      Notes: Reprinted from Evaluation, v.1:no.2 (1973). Copy 2.
  - The Industrial Development Corporation: Its Objectives, Functions, and Problems, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: The Industrial Development Corporation: Its Objectives, Functions, and Problems, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman; Helmut J. Golatz
    - Item 2: The Industrial Development Corporation: Its Objectives, Functions, and Problems, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Investment in Human Resources: How Do We Assess the Costs and Benefits of Manpower Training, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Item 1: Investment in Human Resources: How Do We Assess the Costs and Benefits of Manpower Training, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
      Notes: Paper presented at the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations seminar on "Urban Manpower Trends and Problems in the 1970s," October 6, 1970.
  - Labor Force Trends and Education and Socialization Patterns: Their Effects on Worker Participation, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: Labor Force Trends and Education and Socialization Patterns: Their Effects on Worker Participation, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman; Marvin E. Rozen
      Notes: Paper presented at the Third World Congress of the International Industrial Relations Association, September 3-7, 1973.
    - Item 2: Labor Force Trends and Education and Socialization Patterns: Their Effects on Worker Participation, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
      Notes: Paper presented at the Third World Congress of the International Industrial Relations Association, September 3-7, 1973. Copy 2.
    - Item 3: Labor Force Trends and Education and Socialization Patterns: Their Effects on Worker Participation, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
      Notes: Paper presented at the Third World Congress of the International Industrial Relations Association, September 3-7, 1973. Copy 3.
  - Manpower Supply and Demand, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Item 1: Manpower Supply and Demand, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman; Anne F. Brown
      Notes: Chapter 2 from Review of Educational Research, v.38:no.4 (1968:Oct.)
    - Item 2: Manpower Supply and Demand, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
      Notes: Chapter 2 from Review of Educational Research, v.38:no.4 (1968:Oct.). Copy 2.
  - The Minimum Wage and Poverty, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Item 1: The Minimum Wage and Poverty, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman; Terry G. Foran
      Notes: Reprinted from Toward Freedom From Want.
    - Item 2: The Minimum Wage and Poverty, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
      Notes: Reprinted from Toward Freedom From Want. Copy 2.
  - Occupational Data Requirements for Educational Planning, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Item 1: Occupational Data Requirements for Educational Planning, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
      Author: Sar A. Levitan; Neil W. Chamberlain; John T. Dunlop; Jacob J. Kaufman
      Notes: Reprinted from Journal of Human Resources, v.1:no.1 (1966:Summer).
  - Poverty Programs in Perspective, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Item 1: Poverty Programs in Perspective, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - The Problem of Chronic Unemployment, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Item 1: The Problem of Chronic Unemployment, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
      Notes: Published in Illinois Business Review, v.18:no.4 (1966:Apr.).
    - Item 2: The Problem of Chronic Unemployment, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
      Notes: Published in Illinois Business Review, v.18:no.4 (1966:Apr.). Copy 2.
  - This Is Pennsylvania, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Item 1: This Is Pennsylvania, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
      Notes: Statement prepared for The Pennsylvania Conference on Food, Nutrition, and Health
  - Bargaining, Information and the Use of Threat, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Item 1: Bargaining, Information and the Use of Threat, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
      Author: Sidney Siegel; Donald L. Harnett
      Notes: Research Bulletin no.21 (1961:June)
  - Conceptual Issues in Cost-Benefit Analysis, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Item 1: Conceptual Issues in Cost-Benefit Analysis, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman; Elchanan Cohn
      Notes: Occasional Paper no.8
  - Establishing Priorities for State Governments, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Item 1: Establishing Priorities for State Governments, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
      Notes: Paper presented at the 20th International Meeting of the Institute of Management Sciences, June 29, 1973
    - Item 2: Establishing Priorities for State Governments, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
      Notes: Paper presented at the 20th International Meeting of the Institute of Management Sciences, June 29, 1973. Copy 2.
  - Free Speech and the Taft-Hartley Law, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Item 1: Free Speech and the Taft-Hartley Law, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
      Notes: Published in Social Science, v.33:no.3 (1958:Summer)
    - Item 2: Free Speech and the Taft-Hartley Law, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
      Notes: Reprinted from Social Science, v.33:no.3 (1958:Summer). Copy 2.
    - Item 3: Free Speech and the Taft-Hartley Law, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
      Notes: Reprinted from Social Science, v.33:no.3 (1958:Summer). Copy 3.
  - ILR International Conference Programme, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Item 1: ILR International Conference Programme, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
      Notes: Programme of the International Conference on Trends in Industrial and Labour Relations, January 9-14, 1972.
  - The Implementation of Cost-Effectiveness Techniques, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Item 1: The Implementation of Cost-Effectiveness Techniques, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman; Teh-wei Hu
      Notes: Paper presented at the 22 International Meeting of the Institute of Management Sciences, July 1975.
  - Proposal for a New Labor Studies Consortium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Item 1: Proposal for a New Labor Studies Consortium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - The Research Potential Related to Law Enforcement and the Administration of Justice, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Item 1: The Research Potential Related to Law Enforcement and the Administration of Justice, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)